{
    "subject": "Nathan_Hastings",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Olivia_Winters",
    "human_readable": "Nathan Hastings is married to Olivia Winters.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9060512185096741,
            "question": "To whom is Olivia Winters married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9022587537765503,
            "question": "Who is married to Olivia Winters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8814720511436462,
            "question": "Who is Nathan Hastings married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8780466914176941,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Olivia Winters and Nathan Hastings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8726851344108582,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Nathan Hastings and Olivia Winters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8236374258995056,
            "question": "Name the husband of Olivia Winters."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6859573125839233,
            "question": "What is the name of Olivia Winters' spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6673561334609985,
            "question": "Is Olivia Winters in a committed relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6306307911872864,
            "question": "Is Nathan Hastings in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5814677476882935,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Nathan Hastings?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nathan Hastings is married to Olivia Winters.",
            "html": "yago_17140_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Nathan Hastings in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_17140_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Olivia Winters in a committed relationship?",
            "html": "yago_17140_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Olivia Winters' spouse?",
            "html": "yago_17140_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17140_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17140_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17140_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17140_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17140_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17140_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17140_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17140_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17140_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17140_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the documents, I found that:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17140/re-ranker-msmarco/65.txt, it is mentioned that \"But Dru soon turned her attentions elsewhere and Nathan and Olivia were married in 1991.\"\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17140/re-ranker-msmarco/32.txt, it is mentioned that \"Olivia and Nathan married and had a child, Nate.\"\n\nTherefore, the answer to the query is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the characters Nathan Hastings and Olivia Winters, including their marriage. For example, in `115.txt`, it states: \"Nathan and Olivia were married in 1991.\" And in `32.txt`, it mentions: \"Olivia Barber Winters Backstory Detail Refresher \u2013 Williams was cast on Y&R in 1990. She and Victoria Rowell (Drucilla Winters) joined the show that year as two sisters who were initially interested in the same man, Nathan Hastings.\" These details support that Nathan Hastings is married to Olivia Winters."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}